<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DabbleWithMe</title>
    <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DabbleWithMe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 14:15:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dabblewithme.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Favorite upgrades to my Ender 3 Pro 3D printer</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/favorite-upgrades-to-my-ender-3-pro-3d-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 14:15:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/favorite-upgrades-to-my-ender-3-pro-3d-printer/</guid>
      <description>I have been using my Ender 3 Pro 3D printer for over a year now. So I have been printing upgrades and also I have purchased some upgrades! Here are some of my favorites.
BLTouch This is probaply one of my favorite upgrades to my 3D printer that I have bought. BLTouch makes the whole bed leveling/tramming process super easy. Configure once and then just print.
Installation is quite easy and then you just need to configure Marlin and dabble with settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 08:47:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! This is basically a guaranteed first post for programmer!
Welcome to my brand spanking new blog. I do not remember how many blogs I&amp;rsquo;ve had but not so many in english. I have some finnish blogs but this is the first english one that will tackle my hobby with 3D printing and tinkering around stuff.
This blog is also my first project with Hugo. So this will be interesting project for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>DablleWithMe.xyz is a blog about dabbling. Well that was clear?
In this blog you will find some blog posts about dabbling with 3D printing, web, code and other random stuff. If you like what this sounds like be sure to follow me in the social media.
This blog is build with Hugoand source code is available on Github. I use UpCloudto run my servers.
Man behind the blog is finnish geek from Kuopio.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
