<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on DabbleWithMe</title>
    <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on DabbleWithMe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 13:14:45 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do I need second 3D printer?</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/do_i_need_second_3d_printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 13:14:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/do_i_need_second_3d_printer/</guid>
      <description>Short answer: no. But&amp;hellip; I really would like one&amp;hellip; At this time I have one Ender 3 Pro printer and it has been going strong for over an year now. There are times that I wish I had second one since this one is doing a long print. I have not yet purchased second printer but hey lets have fun thinking of it!
The Dream Prusa. I really would like to have Prusa printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some issues with my BigTreeTech TFT35 E3 v3.0 touch display</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/some-issues-with-my-bigtreetech-tft35-e3-v30-touch-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:56:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/some-issues-with-my-bigtreetech-tft35-e3-v30-touch-display/</guid>
      <description>Well here it comes. Some list of issues that I have at the moment with my TFT35 E3 v3.0 touch display. I will update this post or make a new post if I get some of them fixed.
M600 / Filament change I tried multicolor printing with filament change middle of the print. I used PrusaSlicer to do M600 (filament change) command on specific layer. It worked just fine with the stock display that my Ender 3 Pro had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite upgrades to my Ender 3 Pro 3D printer</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/favorite-upgrades-to-my-ender-3-pro-3d-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 14:15:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/favorite-upgrades-to-my-ender-3-pro-3d-printer/</guid>
      <description>I have been using my Ender 3 Pro 3D printer for over a year now. So I have been printing upgrades and also I have purchased some upgrades! Here are some of my favorites.
BLTouch This is probaply one of my favorite upgrades to my 3D printer that I have bought. BLTouch makes the whole bed leveling/tramming process super easy. Configure once and then just print.
Installation is quite easy and then you just need to configure Marlin and dabble with settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 08:47:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabblewithme.xyz/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! This is basically a guaranteed first post for programmer!
Welcome to my brand spanking new blog. I do not remember how many blogs I&amp;rsquo;ve had but not so many in english. I have some finnish blogs but this is the first english one that will tackle my hobby with 3D printing and tinkering around stuff.
This blog is also my first project with Hugo. So this will be interesting project for that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
